<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Afghanistan on Masood Sadat Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/afghanistan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Afghanistan on Masood Sadat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/afghanistan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tuturial for Analysing Survey of the Afghan People in R</title>
      <link>/2018/05/31/a-tuturial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/31/a-tuturial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</guid>
      <description>About the Survey of the Afghan People Since 2006, The Asia Foundation conducts the Survey of the Afghan People, a nationally-representative annual survey. The Survey reflects perceptions about a broad range of topics including security, development, governance, service delivery, women’s rights, and migration. The Survey is broadly used by policy makers, academics, non-governmental organizations working in and on Afghanistan.
The data for all waves of the survey is publicly available on the Asia Foundation website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceptions About Electricity in Afghanistan: Insights From the Survey of the Afghan People</title>
      <link>/2018/05/10/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/10/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan/</guid>
      <description>About This analysis is prepared following a requrest from Peter Stevenson of Mercy Corps–Afghanistan.
This analysis uses the Survey of the Afghan People data, an annual survey of perceptions from a nationally representative sample of Afghans. The survey has collected attitudes and perceptions uninterruptedly since 2006, with over 97,000 Afghans taking part. The the latest survey report here, or download the raw data here.  Awareness of Government Supplied Electricity Projects  Key Questions: x11as.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>