<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Masood Sadat Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Masood Sadat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Missing Values</title>
      <link>/2018/05/22/plot-missing-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/22/plot-missing-values/</guid>
      <description>In one of DataCamp courses that I cannot remember which one, the instructor used geom_tile from ggplot2 package to visualize missing values. Here, I am going to replicate that using airquality dataset from base R.
To start, we can use summary() and str() functions to inspect the data.
summary(airquality) ## Ozone Solar.R Wind Temp ## Min. : 1.00 Min. : 7.0 Min. : 1.700 Min. :56.00 ## 1st Qu.: 18.00 1st Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of GitHub through command line</title>
      <link>/2018/05/18/basics-of-github-through-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/18/basics-of-github-through-command-line/</guid>
      <description>Create account and repository on github.com Go to github.com and create an account. Once, account is created, create a repository in Repositories tab and click on the green button New. The following page opens.
 NOTE: A repository is something like a project folder.
   Copy repository URL After a new repository is created, copy the clone url link. This link is used to clone the repository from server to the computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceptions About Electricity in Afghanistan: Insights From the Survey of the Afghan People</title>
      <link>/2018/05/10/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/10/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan/</guid>
      <description>About This analysis is prepared following a requrest from Peter Stevenson of Mercy Corps–Afghanistan.
This analysis uses the Survey of the Afghan People data, an annual survey of perceptions from a nationally representative sample of Afghans. The survey has collected attitudes and perceptions uninterruptedly since 2006, with over 97,000 Afghans taking part. The the latest survey report here, or download the raw data here.  Awareness of Government Supplied Electricity Projects  Key Questions: x11as.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Masood Sadat, from Afghanistan living in Kabul. I am trained in economics but my interest transcends economics to all social sciences, technology and data science. In addition to my formal education, which I owe a lot of my knowledge to, I have been self-learning and teaching others topics in data analysis and data science since 2014. I start this website/blog to share custom analysis I carry out every now and then, R and Stata tips and tricks, and other related posts for anyone interested and for my future self.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>